It's Straw Hat and Jinbe!
They're crazy strong!
Watch out!
Why didn't they mention "Black Leg"?!
Just run!
I know!
I wanna kick Kaido's ass!
Stop!
You won't get through!
You weaklings are pathetic!
Forgive us... Master Hamlet,
Master Fourtricks...
We couldn't stop them!
"Ordinary"?
A fitting word for rabble such as yourself!
"Expectations"?
Those are for us to surpass!
Quiet yourself, Hamlet.
The truly powerful remain silent.
– Master Hamlet!
– Master Fourtricks!
That looks wrong!
– Master Hamlet!
– Master Fourtricks!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Kiku!
Get away from the rooftop!
Yes, sir!
Then... if you would...
Can you stand, Kikunojo?
Of course.
That's more like it...
Your determination never runs dry.
I love...
the way of the samurai.
Roger...
Whitebeard...
Now they did it right!
Call me old-fashioned, but...
death completes a man.
Do you not agree?
Let's finish this!
Stow your arrogance, Kaido!
There is no honor in falling by your hand!
None!
How are you enjoying my plague rounds?!
No way...
It's cold...
Help me, please...!
Hold on, stop!
We're on the same side!
Your Awesomeness,
why did you shoot us, too?!
It's cold! It's cold! I'm becoming an ogre...
Help me, please!
All you guys do is laugh anyway!
Make yourselves useful for once, Pleasures!
Help me...
There was still some humanity left in him!
Either way, he was going to become
an ogre soon. The outcome is the same.
I suppose that's true.
More importantly, where did
the commander go?
No idea!
We need to focus on survival!
No mercy even for their allies?!
Omasa!
Dammit...!
I'm sorry, Boss Hyogoro...
I'll die before I hurt any of you!
Don't jump the gun, you fool!
I don't want to be an ogre!
There must be a cure!
I'll cut you down myself
if there's no other option!
There's no need to end it yourself!
If this goes on...
Is there anything you can do, Chopper?!
Realistically, it's not possible to develop a cure
in the middle of battle, let alone distribute it.
Then...
But unlike back in Udon, we have
the guy who made the virus right here!
Whoever created the virus would have also created
an antibody at the same time and kept it around.
If I get that antibody,
I can synthesize a ton of medicine!
Of all the people to have it, it's a Superstar!
Getting it will be next to impossible!
Forget the aggression, I'm more concerned about
what's going to happen if we leave them like this!
Not only are their muscles and ferocity growing,
their skin is cooling unusually fast!
Their bodies won't be able to handle it!
How do I keep these guys
from getting back up?
Are they zombies?!
So you're saying that if we
leave them like this...
They'll die!
Once you get infected, you only
have an hour left at the most!
What?!
Was the person who turned
into an ice ogre your best friend?
Your boss?
Your subordinate?
I'm sure they've never felt as full of energy
as they do right this very second!
Make sure you give 'em one last big hug!
But you might catch the bug!
Dammit, Queen!
How could he make another
messed-up weapon like this?!
I gotta get the hell off this floor!
Hey! Open the door!
Hey! Brother Apoo!
What's this?
That right there is the only antibody
in the whole world!
Oh, for Ice Ogre?
If you lose it, your punishment will be
one hell of a brutal death...
Death...?
– An antibody...
...against Ice Ogre?
What? What?!
Whaaat?!
Queen presents!
Game... Time!
Zoomin', zoomin', zoomin', zoomin'
Let's party hardy buddy,
'cause it's time to play!
A game just ain't a game
if it ain't got any stakes!
Murder! Betrayal! There ain't no rules today!
'Cause in an hour, sucka, you are gonna...
die!
It's a plague!
That bastard!
Are people's lives worth nothing to him?!
Ice ogre...
tag!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Zoro! Get that antibody from him!
Got it!
Don't let them have it!
Our men are gonna die!
Don't let the samurai recover!
Hold on a second, Queen!
You crazy-ass bastard!
Start!
Steal it from each other!
Murder for it!
As long as you don't
get caught, you win, Apoo!
Everyone else will die!
Dammit!
You really think you can outrun us
while carrying them?
Anyway, as long as we kill the brat,
our mission is complete.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
Why do you...
fight for the Kozuki?
I do not know who you are,
but if you are on our side...
please save Lord Momonosuke!
I'm saving you, too, Shinobu!
What?
Twenty years ago...
I witnessed Kozuki Oden's execution firsthand!
Don't you understand that you
owe your peaceful lives to him?!
Lord Oden has always been
this country's guardian!
Now, can you still call him a fool?!
Tell me!
Your speech brought me to tears!
Not only that...
Kozuki Oden's way of life
brought me to tears, too!
Momonosuke.
On that terrible day,
in order to save you...
I ran to Kuri.
What?! Then how... are you alive?
But...
I'm sorry...
All I could do was watch as Kaido
dangled you over the edge!
Back then,
I wasn't strong enough!
Huh?
Wh-Who are you?
You identified yourself as my father...
Kozuki Oden!
My other name is...
Yamato!
And I...
would die for you!
Marco!
I may not understand
my role in this war just yet...
but I know better than the Straw Hats
how dangerous you are!
Hey! Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Ready?!
Heavenly Feuer!
There's no room for you
on the ships bound for the new era!
Keep your mouth shut!
Why are his flames overpowering mine?!
Prometheus!
Phoenix flames...
are of legendary stock!
Why, you little...
How dare you?!
You let your guard down, huh?
Good luck getting away now!
Take the shot, Perospero!
Okay, Mama!
Lick.
Sorry, Marco...
I'll be letting Mama help me out!
Damn...
There were so many other times where
I relished the thought of killing you.
How ironic.
Goodbye...
– Moon...
– Raid!
I-It's you again! From before!
You keep getting in my way!
Is this the man who killed Pedro?!
Yes!
If it weren't for him...
That idiot Pedro blew himself up!
He caused trouble for me!
I'm certain that Pedro's death
is what led us to this battle.
You-gara must press on!
Oh, this is just perfect!
Don't bring something as petty as revenge...
to the edge of a battlefield!
Well, do whatever you want!
Who are you two?!
Carrot.
Wanda.
And you're Marco.
A friend of Master Nekomamushi's, right?
I guess you could say that...
Marco!
If you wanna kill me,
it'll have to be some other time!
I don't wanna waste
any souls on you right now!
Go, Marco!
Leave him to us!
Alright, I'm counting on you!
What is that?
Hold it!
Give me that!
Stop chasing me!
Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Two against one isn't fair!
Man...!
I'd rather be helping out Kin'emon!
Fighting you is a huge waste of time!
And I've always hated you!
The feeling's mutual, jackass!
Drake... that asshole...
Can't believe he did a complete 180
after getting caught!
I see...
So that's Roronoa Zoro.
Better take out Straw Hat's
number two and three as soon as possible.
Speaking of which...
I had no idea Judge's son was on their crew.
Vinsmoke Judge's son, Sanji!
I thought I would turn into an ogre...
But look at me!
I'm just fine!
Good!
You don't have skin or veins,
and you can't get cold,
so you're practically a corpse!
Oh, I see!
I suppose my body's always
been like a frigid corpse!
That's why I'm not becoming
an ice ogre even though I was infected...
It's a little sad!
But that means I'm invincible!
Wait a minute...
Brook's a skeleton, so his temperature
didn't change even when he was infected.
That's why the virus didn't multiply.
But when a normal person
is infected, their body grows cold.
That's what allows the virus
to multiply rapidly...
So if we can find a way
to maintain their temperature...
But wait...
how does it freeze them from the inside?
Is this...
Maybe this virus is...
Chopper!
Look at your arm!
What?!
Oh no! I didn't notice!
Chopper's gonna die!
Lethal Green Star!
Devil!
Ew, ew! So gross!
Alright, got her!
Now dissolve her with your
super-strong digestive juices!
So slimy... so sticky!
Save me, Pay-Pay!
You totally could have freed yourself!
Devil!
Pay-Pay, I love you!
Stop! You're all slimy and gross!
I love you so much!
D-D-Damn you!
How about this?!
Bamboo Javelin!
What a boring attack.
I'm not doing this just to have
a good time, you know!
Oh, crap!
Ulti-Mortar!
Again?!
Usopp...
Hey, tramp!
Stop!
Don't kill me! I surrender! You win!
It's pretty damn obvious that you lost!
Now, say it!
Say what?
I already told you how pissed I am!
After all, your captain said he'll take down
Kaido and become King of the Pirates!
I'm sorry!
Luffy...
is a complete idiot!
So please don't headbutt me!
Please!
I'll leave the island...
I-If you do it again, I'll...
actually die!
Then say it!
Say that your captain...
will never become the King of the Pirates!
Okay...
Luffy will...
Luffy will... Luffy will...
never...
That's it, Nami...
It's okay to lie...
If you don't choose your words
carefully, you'll wind up dead!
After you've come so far!
Lie!
Just lie to her!
Luffy will...
never...
stop until he's the Pirate King!
I'm sure of it!
He will be...
Because...
Because... Because...
That's just how it is!
Very well, then!
Die.
Nami, you moron!
Just run!
Onami!
Go! Komachiyo!
A dog?!
What?!
Is that...
...Otama?!
What are you doing here?!